Cinderella
Cinderella's Sister
Episode 16
I don't know what is happening right now...
Please try to tell me.
Business K: The person who lives again through Dae Seong Saccaromycetes.
This is...
So if this were America, it'd be like the TIME magazine or the New York whatever.
I'm saying this isn't something anyone can get their faces on.
You have to be someone who could show up on the 9 o'clock news at least a few times
to get your face printed on the cover of this booklet.
MMM
Noisy Caller
Where are you?
How could you leave like that?
Goo Hyo Seon
Hello?
I just saw the magazine.
Where is it?
I'm saying I saw the magazine.
The magazine that has Dad's face on it...
Where are you?
I'm on my way to Dong Soo's.
You're going to Dong Soo's?
Business K: The person who lives again through Dae Seong Saccaromycetes.
Yes.
There's a rice wine tasting competition later tonight.
Dong Soo told me to come a bit early.
Hello? Hello?
Dong Soo
Dong Soo, don't tell Hyo Seon anything!
What do you mean?
The things you told me earlier. Hyo Seon can't know that.
Really?
Okay. Aren't you coming?
Hurry up. You need to come, too.
I wonder. I don't think I'll be able to make it, Hyo Seon.
Do you know what's going on here now?
The phones have started ringing off the hook now. Wait a moment.
Thank you. This is Dae Seong True Winemakers.
Of course you can order right now. How much do you need?
Yes, yes I understand.
Could you please email us your order form?
Yes. Yes, thank you.
Hello. Did you hear that?
Yes. I heard it. That's a relief.
But here too, I didn't just come to this tasting contest to play and have fun.
I was hoping it would help us promote our wine.
Think of it as work and I want you to make time to come.
Hello, this is Dae Seong True Winemakers
The person who lives again through Dae Seong Saccaromycetes.
Hyo Seon can't know about it!
Dae Seong True Winemakers
Eun Jo. I'm okay, can you open up?
Eun Jo. Are you okay?
Open up.
Hong Gi Hoon, who works at your company, is their youngest son.
Did you know that?
You're quick.
I did think you'd come find me again,
but this is sooner than I expected.
How many brothers do you have?
You have a younger brother, right?
Did my younger brother wrong you?
He practically lives his day to day with a picture of your sister, Goo Hyo Seon.
Did he seek your home, by chance?
He won't mature, despite his age.
If he's made some kind of mistake, I'll apologize on his behalf.
I'm not sure I understand what you mean.
Didn't you ask about my younger brother?
Yes, I did.
What was your question?
Do you have a younger brother named Hong Gi Hoon?
So you do.
I understand.
Sit.
I said sit. A conversation can't be one-sided.
My younger brother's name is Hong Gi Tae.
That guy named Hong Gi Hoon is not my brother.
Although he's not my brother,
he is indeed my father's son.
It seems like you know something. You can ask for the details from Gi Hoon or my father.
I have nothing to tell you.
So...
all Hong Joo Ga's family members worked together,
along with Hong Gi Hoon...
Stop.
This isn't something you should be saying to me.
I didn't ask you to sit here for me to hear this.
If you find out about the truth from Gi Hoon or my father,
you'll definitely want to meet me again.
That means I would want to cooperate with you to do absolutely anything.
Let's talk again then.
Excuse me.
There has never been anyone who gets up before I do.
Why not?
There also hasn't been anyone who asks that.
Eun Jo, now I really
can't go ...
to you...
At least you can repay Ahjusshi like this.
I don't have a way to repay him.
I'm jealous you have a way.
It's already too late. I can't.
The person who lives again through Dae Seong Saccaromycetes.
Take her home.
Okay, I got it.
What are you guys doing?
So...
you people colluded
and killed someone.
I thought I had done that...
So ...
I wasn't the only one...
who was pushing down my dad.
So many people against one person...
And ...
that person was part of it too, wasn't he?
That person...
colluded with you guys, didn't he?
So many people against one person...
This means ...
so many people ...
ganged up like that
on one person.
Hey, you're really pale.
Are you okay?
What are you going to do?
You guys are in serious trouble.
I'm not going to let this go.
What are you going to do?
Sit here.
What do you want?
I'm hungry.
I didn't eat anything this morning.
Has your fever gone down?
Your cold hasn't gone away yet, right?
I'm fine.
What do you want?
I just...
didn't want to eat alone.
That's not like you.
Whether you care for me or not,
you're not someone who would call me because you don't want to eat alone.
Did Mom perhaps say something to you?
Mom?
Never mind, if that's not it.
How are you feeling inside?
You said you're heartbroken. How are you feeling?
Don't misunderstand me.
Because you're broken hearted, I can't help that.
That's not what I mean.
Are you curious
about what it's like?
Yes, I am. I said I would care more about you, didn't I?
You might not believe me, but as your sister,
or as a friend you keep seeing a lot of these days,
I have the right to ask, don't I?
Are you really curious?
Yes.
I'm curious.
It hurts.
Officially getting rejected
really hurts.
What kind of person is he?
What do you mean?
You two were close like siblings much longer than I knew him.
I'm just curious.
How did he join our family?
Dad brought him in one day.
He is the son of Dad's friend. He didn't have money for tuition, so he came to work part-time.
Do you still have feelings for him?
What do you think?
I'm asking because I don't know.
Yes.
Even if Oppa leaves...even if he goes to another woman...
even if I become someone who has nothing to do with him...
Thanks for being curious about me.
But still, I think you and I should get our stories in sync at least.
I don't know just how much the eldest daughter knew before coming to see me,
but now she knows that you're our father's son,
doesn't that mean she knows why you went working there?
That girl seems to believe that you and I have been conspiring against them.
Because she seems so confident, things like legal action or reporting to the newspaper,
it seemed like she'd be the kind of brazen puppy to do those kinds of things.
How was Eun Jo?
How she was... What does that mean?
Did she cry?
I'm not sure.
I can't remember if she cried or not but she was shaking like a leaf.
At the very least to make sure that girl doesn't run around wild, you'll have to take care of her.
If she does, won't that be difficult for you, me, or our father?
She's not here yet.
Where did she go, shaking like she was?
Are you listening to what I'm saying or not? What nonsense are you spewing?
Where did she go?!
Did you just let that girl, who was shaking like that, go alone?
Why didn't you call me before letting her leave like that?!
He looks a little uncertain.
The next person up is Miss Goo Hyo Seon. Applause.
Oh my god, what's going on? What's wrong with her?
- I don't think she's sure.
- How can Goo Hyo Seon not know?
Shouldn't she know Dae Seong True Winemakers, her family's own wine?
- She's not sure.
- What's wrong with her?
Hyo Seon should know it, obviously.
Why isn't she saying anything?
- She can't seem to taste it.
Why can't she?
Next person up will be Kim In Gyeong.
Let's go. We need to talk.
All right!
That's all right!
Next up is participant Lee Hyo Jae.
Let's talk.
About what? I have nothing to say to you.
Let go.
- I have something to say.
- No! I'm not going to listen.
I tried to tell you before. I didn't want you to find out from someone else.
Eun Jo. Eun Jo.
Let go! Let go!
I said to let go of me!
Eun Jo. Eun Jo!
- Eun Jo, wait -
- Let go. Let go, let go!
Let go!
I said let go.
Let go...
What excuses are you trying to make?
I can't hear it yet.
If I listen to you, I think my body will explode, shatter, and disappear!
You bastard.
You're the worst son of a b**ch in the world. You're the ground.
Even from ground level, none could be worse.
I don't even want to step on you! Disgusting!
Listen to me now. Just listen right now.
Let go! I don't want to!
Right now. If a day passes, it'll be that much pain. If two days pass, it'll be two days worth of pain.
I'll end it for you now. Let's end it here!
Let go.
Where did Oppa Gi Hoon and Unni Eun Jo go?
They left for some work at the factory.
Is it really for work at the factory?
Yes. It's really for work at the factory.
What work at the factory?
I'm not sure about that either.
What relationship do you and Eun Jo have?
Did Eun Jo not tell you?
She doesn't talk about that kind of stuff. You know how she is.
When we were younger, we lived in the same house once.
In the same house?
Yes, in the same house.
Before Noona came, there was no one who cooked for us...
In the same house, even with my Mom?
Yes.
I don't think Mom knows you.
Ajhumma was never interested in me.
Of course she doesn't know me.
Did Mom...
live with your dad?
No, he's not my father. He's just someone who raised me.
Is his name...
Jang Taek Geun?
It's not.
It's really not.
Can you let me meet him?
Why would you meet him? There's no need.
So Jang Taek Geun is your father.
That's what it is...
All of you... There's something wrong with you people.
Right?
How could you all... step foot into our household?
About that, I-
Shut it.
Shut that mouth.
Don't say a word.
No matter what it was, you shouldn't have done it.
No matter what your father told you,
Whatever that family is like
your household's obstacles, you can't endure them.
Even to an elder who took you in without any qualms,
you lied to him,
you lied to Hyo Seon who's like a sister to you,
and to me?
It's because of my mom.
When I heard my mom died because of my older brother, I went crazy.
I would have gone to any length to destroy him.
I was going to return the winery back to Ahjussi and ruin my older brother.
That's all I could think of. I didn't do anything other than that.
I was out of my mind.
I...
Hyo Seon...
And that elder could never have imagined this even in our dreams.
Seeing us so easily fooled. Did it make you feel good?
Even after he passed because there were just two girls left, did it seem so easy to you?
How did it make you feel to see Hyo Seon like you like crazy?
Seeing me as an idiot, who can't still get over you! Was it fun?
Do you want to die?
You want to die?
Do you really want to die?
I let it all slip through my hands.
Ahjussi... You... I lost it all.
Where I had lost it. I saw it in front of me, and yet I couldn't pick it up. That me
you're asking that to me? Whether it was fun?
Even knowing what crimes I committed, thinking non-stop if there were a way I could have you.
You're asking that of me? How I felt?
Even if I died and dropped into the depths of hell--!
Shut your mouth.
You terrible girl.
If it was so easy?
Are you asking if I had fun?
Just try to open your mouth to Hyo Seon to beg for her forgiveness.
Just try to make her suffer again to shrug off your own guilt.
I'm sure you want to leave here immediately but you can't.
As planned, everything is finished so now you quietly go on your way.
Tell Hyo Seon to be well as if you're just going to do your military service.
And if she needs you anytime,
don't ever forget to tell her you're going to act like an Oppa.
If Hyo Seon becomes tormented and looks for you.
Don't forget. Go to her and comfort her.
Live like that way for the rest of your life.
It might be torturous to you but it's the least you have to do.
That's the only way
to prevent me from killing you,
from taking any more actions here.
That's the only way to let go of you.
♫  Again today my memory led me astray  ♫
♫  I who am strolling at the end of the street  ♫
♫  where you can't hold me again  ♫
♫  I ask again about the way  ♫
♫  Saying I want to see you and hold you again  ♫
♫  While looking at heaven I'm praying  ♫
♫  It must be you  ♫
♫  I cannot be without you  ♫
♫  Like this for another day, month or year  ♫
♫  I don't mind even if I am hurt  ♫
♫  I don't mind even if my heart breaks  ♫
♫  because, yes, you are the only one I love  ♫
Noona.
Jeong Woo. I don't know what it is...
but I can't hear anything right now.
I can't. You already know.
♫  I'm saying I can't let you go a second time  ♫
♫  I'm saying I can't forget you and live  ♫
♫  It must be you  ♫
♫  I cannot be without you  ♫
♫  Like this for another day, month or year  ♫
♫  The love I will protect  ♫
♫  The love I love  ♫
♫  Because for me  ♫
♫  Yes, if it's just you, it is enough  ♫
♫  because you are the only one I love.  ♫
What is it?
Mom and Little Noona are gone.
What?
They're gone.
Where to?
I don't know.
Mom
The person you're calling is not available.
You are being directed to voicemail...
Goo Hyo Seon
The person you're calling is not available.
You are being directed to voicemail...
Lead the way.
Did you have to go this far?
Did we have to ride the train all night to come this far and do this?
Think about how you'd feel if you were me.
I fall for a certain woman at first sight.
I grab on to her skirt, following her around. I made her my mom.
I didn't doubt that my dad was happy because of that woman.
So, even though I knew that woman didn't sincerely like me...
I was still thankful for those eight years.
My gratitude,
my dad's love for my mom,
they all became dirty.
Fine. Even if you do say those things, it is useless.
Tell me what good you think this is going to do.
Those words are useless?
According to whom?
That's not how you should treat people's hearts.
We're not cows, pigs, or even dogs!
We're people.
But Mom, you treated Dad and me like we were pigs.
Like we were dogs.
I can't believe you still don't realize it.
I don't know how it's possible that Mom doesn't know that.
The frustration makes me want to dig a thousand meters into the ground and bury myself in it!
So what good is all this going to do?!
It's all over. We're seeing each other's faces needlessly because of you!
There's no need to see?
You still have his number! You can contact each other if you have the will to do so?!
I didn't have his number. I got rid of it!
It's because you scolded me that I remembered the number that I had forgotten, you terrible girl.
Don't say Eun Jo is spiteful.
You're even a thousand times, ten thousands times more spiteful!
Please come in.
Come in.
Excuse me.
Please take our order.
What to do today for the future
Stay there for an hour. I just need an hour.
Sojeongri Station Train Schedule
Seoul - Chuncheon - Gangneung - Seoul - Gangneung - Daegu - Pusan
Daegu - Busan - Chuncheon
Busan
Seoul - Chuncheon - Gangneung
Chuncheon - Seoul - Gangneung
Aren't you Kang Sook by any chance?
Don't you recognize me?
Hey I even aided you postpartum.
What's this? I even recognized you right away.
Jin... Jin Ah Mi?
That's right, Jin Ah Mi. I'm Jin Ah Mi, you wench.
What's this?
Who did you snare to make you look like such a lady?
You're not someone I'm fond of, so let's each pour our own drinks.
I don't have any reason to see anyone from your family any more.
If you have something to say, let's get it over with quickly, Miss.
The person who lives again through Dae Seong Saccaromycetes.
Please take a look at this. It's my dad.
This is my dad.
He was really a great man.
I've never seen a man as great as my dad ever since I was born in this world.
I'm not saying this because he's my father. He was really a great man, Ahjussi.
You know Eun Jo, right?
You don't even know how much Eun Jo also loved and respected my dad.
If she didn't love my dad as much as she did,
I would have kicked her out already.
Because she loves my dad,
I'm just tolerating her.
My dad to me, you know,
was that kind of person.
But, my dad loved Mom very much.
He sincerely loved her.
Even knowing Mom was meeting you, he did not show that he knew.
The reason he didn't is because he was afraid Mom would leave.
Ahjussi.
I know you're not going to see Mom again.
I didn't know
but now that I've met you, I'm sure you won't.
But, what I wanted to say wasn't this.
Ahjussi.
Can't you sincerely apologize to my dad?
As long as I know, I can't sleep.
If someone who needs to apologize, doesn't do so,
my dad is too pitiful.
That's why I'm asking.
Ahjussi, you know you were wrong.
It's true that you seduced a woman who was married!
You know that's wrong to do!
My mom was bad
but my mom to me not only is sufficiently being punished by me
My mom truly is pounding on her own chest
and is regretful.
So if you apologize, that should be enough.
Ahjussi, you should feel bad toward my dad.
If you a human being.
Don't you agree?
I asked if you agreed, Ahjussi!
Please give us more wine here.
Yes.
Ahjussi, please give us Dae Seong True Winemakers' takju.
Dae Seong True Winemakers' takju!
But, it's a little more expensive.
Do you want me to exchange for a cheaper one?
Ahjussi, when did you start getting this again?
Yesterday.
Really?
Even if they're expensive, they seem to sell well.
My dad's...
It's my dad's wine.
Miss.
If you're saying this to this extent to m, what must your state of mind be?
I'm not a human, but a beast.
Think that a human didn't do it.
Then you'll feel a bit less wronged.
If you listen to the sounds of a beast, I'll speak.
I'm very sorry.
My face is so red from shame, that I cannot bring myself to bow at your father's grave.
Please tell him for me.
I'm very sorry.
Sincerely.
The person who lives again through Dae Seong Saccaromycetes.
Number 1 in the country!
Dae Seong True Winemakers' Takju is made with domestic yeast!
Domestic first! Korean yeast.
Hey! We're in trouble. Big trouble.
Is there anything we can do to just shake everything off with our hands. The orders are pouring in.
I don't know if we'll be able to fill the orders.
I don't know if we need to change this right here into a factory-style.
If by chance feel we can't fulfill the order
then we might just raze this over and turn it into a factory.
Setting up a factory here means
everyone here isn't needed!
Hey you! Do you know what I'm saying?
Hey.
Noona, it's me.
Did something happen at the brewery?
No, that's not it.
If not, let's talk later. I'm hanging up.
That girl.
Goo Eun Jo, let's talk for a bit.
I don't understand what is going on at all. What is it?
Never mind. It's not something you need to worry about anymore.
You really don't ever loosen up.
What did you want to tell me?
When was it that you requested something of me? And now you say--
Thank you. I said thank you.
I'll treat you to a meal. Or did you want a bribe?
So what did you want to tell me?
I'm getting married.
Really? Congratulations.
When is it?
It's all written in there. One is for Hyo Seon, and the other one is for that hyung.
Does that hyung not like me?
So he probably won't come to my wedding?
I'll give it to him.
Is there something wrong with Hyo Seon's taste buds?
It's because she has a severe cold.
That doesn't seem to be the case.
You should take her to the hospital. She said no matter if it's rice,
side dishes or alcohol, everything tastes like water to her.
It seems like she has completely lost her taste buds. Completely.
It's not salty at all.
Goo Hyo Seon
The number you have dialed is turned off...
Mom
The person you're calling is not able to take your call.
Han Jeong Woo
Jeong Woo, you can tell me now. I'm not as busy now.
You seemed very tired so I couldn't say anything earlier.
Joon Soo's second noona...
found out about Ajusshi Jang.
There were some things she found out herself, but I also...let a few things slip.
What's wrong?
It's like a lie...
Everything is like a lie...
What should we do...with Hyo Seon?
That's why she's sick...
That's why she can't taste anything...
What should I do?
Hello?
Joon Soo...
Second Noona, where's Mom?
Mom...didn't go home?
I don't know! Why isn't she back?!
The last bus has left, Customer.
So, this is how you're going to be...
Mom,
is this how you are going to do it?
Mom...
Mom!
Mom, don't go!
♫  It must be you  ♫
♫  I cannot be without you ♫
♫  Like this for another day, month or year  ♫
♫  I don't mind even if I am hurt  ♫
♫  I don't mind even if my heart breaks  ♫
♫  because, yes, you are the only one I love  ♫
♫  My bruised heart is shouting so that I can find you.  ♫
♫  Wherever you are  ♫
♫  Can't you hear my voice?  ♫